Everything's all set.
I can bring down this building any time.
I'm feeling confident about my mana.
So if anything happens to the others, I can cover for them.
This is enough, right?
I'm using magic to knock the dragon out.
Instead of trying to hit it directly and risk hurting the others in the crossfire,
I'm gonna collapse a building on top of it.
Yeah, this is the best way.
Stay calm.
I have to focus on the job I was given.
We'll make this work.
Valon, just hold out for us.
It's us!
Run!
It's fast!
Fun fact, red dragons can run up to 60 kilometers per hour!
That's fun!
It's fine, the terrain's slowing it down!
Up ahead, turn right!
Now we baited fire breath down this corridor!
Dragons store fuel in their bellies, and click their tongue to ignite it!
For our own safety!
We have to make it exhaust all of its fuel!
It's tonguing!
Look out!
Such intense heat!
But...
We can handle it thanks to the pan and spells!
Yes!
We've got the...
Oh, no!
The heat from the pan...
It's spreading evenly...
Cut!
Oh, yeah, of course it's hot!
Since he was cooking with that pan every single day!
I assumed it would be able to repel dragon fire!
According to Namari, adamantine is supposed to block all attacks from a dragon!
I think she was making stuff up!
Was not...
Here it comes!
Damn it!
I've got a change course!
Let's go back!
Hmm?
Huh?
What?
They're here?
Already?
But why?
I thought that we were supposed to stay split up!
Should I still do things according to plan?
Ah, fine then!
Here I go!
Oh, my God!
Are you kidding me?
It didn't work!
Quiet!
Don't move!
The inverse scale's right there!
If I get a bit closer, it's mine!
It made a run for it!
Damn it, Tensuke!
You're just a monster after...
Did you?
You two!
Get up!
Hurry!
Up up us!
Get under its belly!
Damn you, Elias!
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
Damn it!
The common language doesn't have enough curse words!
Punza!
Valo!
Please, don't cuss at me in a language I don't speak, Chilchak!
Any plans, genius?
Look really mad!
This way!
Let's run out the tail slide!
On second thought, nixed that.
This is where we live now, under the red dragon's crotch.
No good.
Simple spells aren't gonna work on it at all!
Focus!
What the hell was that?
Did you just go and shatter our last weapon?
How do we fix this mess?
No choice.
Use this.
Huh?
Does this mean that knife is made from a special metal?
It cuts the bones and skin of any monster.
I've never gone a day without taking good care of it.
It's a mithril kitchen knife.
Maybe the only one of its kind in the world.
Mithril?
Seriously?
Wish we could have shown Namaari.
Pretty sure she would have killed Senshi if we had.
Yeah, I had a feeling that was the case, so I kept my mouth shut.
Take this!
Whoa!
It really pierced right through the scales!
But with the size of this blade, no matter where I stabbed, I doubt I'd be able to fatally wound it.
Oh, crap!
What now?
This means that the plan failed, doesn't it?
Or is this some sort of new one?
What the heck do I do?
There's no time to hesitate!
Stop!
Get back!
I'm getting farther from my sword.
We're gonna end up in the town square if we keep backing up.
And then we'll get burnt to a crisp!
I'll distract the dragon.
No, you can't!
Lyos, I know you know this.
Of all the monsters that we've eaten so far,
were there any that didn't fight until their last breath?
It's eat or be eaten here.
If we don't give it our all, then we're gonna be some monsters' dinner.
Here, prepare yourself!
Sensei!
No, stop!
There's no point in just running out there!
Go find Marcel!
You two think of a new plan!
Hey, are you alive?
I'll get this off!
Huh?
Can you move?
I did it!
Why is this thing stuck to the ground?
I'll be right back!
Come on!
Get up!
Sensei!
Sorry, Marcel!
I didn't know you were here.
Uh, good to know that the spell is working.
What's going on?
Where are the others?
It's not looking too good.
All the plans we had set up failed.
The other two are still out there with the dragon.
Huh?
What should we do?
Does that mean we have to use my magic?
The dragon is wounded and violent.
It'll be too dangerous to get near it.
But we have to do something and fast.
Let's move upward.
Huh?
To do what?
We'll get level with the dragon's face.
And I'll get on the pan.
The pan?
And once I'm there, you'll blow it up.
What?
It's been blinded in its left eye.
So if we approach from that side, we should be able to jump on it without being noticed.
Are you sure?
Marcel, you did something similar before, didn't you?
Back when you fought the Undine.
Yeah, but at the time, I had water walking in water.
I have the pan and abjuration magic.
And then what?
How will you hit the inverse scale while clinging to its face?
Don't worry.
I've got an idea.
We can't make any more mistakes.
I've no intention to.
I'm a little hesitant that this is going to work, but...
I trust you.
I'm a little hesitant.
You're going to get flung off.
Hurry and go through with the plan.
It'll be over fast.
It's not that big a deal.
Compared to what Valon went through.
This is nothing!
Lyos, no!
No!
Okay.
I don't know.
Help me.
So cold.
Can't breathe.
Rallin, run.
Bios!
Leave my brother...
alone!
The person in that grave there...
His ring is binding his soul here.
Please remove it.
The ghost will then be freed.
His ring?
Is this real?
This is the grave of Oldman who died recently.
When he was alive, he bragged about how he bought a golden ring from an elf.
But how would a child know about that?
Did I...
Do something bad?
No, you did great, Fallon.
Ghost magic is a cool talent to have.
Don't be sad.
Grownups are just scared of magic.
I think you should go and study it for real.
It'll help you get work, you know?
It will?
Probably.
You could try priest, grave keeper...
Ooh, traveling exorcist might be fun too.
You could wander across the lands and help people who need you.
Wow, I like that.
Would you be able to come with me too, brother?
Of course.
Where should we go first?
Hmm...
How about the ocean?
Ooh, or the desert!
I hear?
There's a country with talking dogs there.
Let's go, please!
But...
It might be best if we don't travel together anymore.
Fallon?
Why?
Don't worry about me.
Goodbye, big brother.
Lyos, you okay?
I stopped the bleeding for now, so hold on a bit longer.
I'll go find the other two, along with your leg!
Don't worry about me, huh?
You really shouldn't say such sad things.
I'm gonna bring you home.
I promise.
Hey!
Chill, Chuck!
Senshi!
Thank goodness!
You okay?
No, you're not.
I need more practice with my abjuration magic, huh?
We're still mostly in one piece, so it could be worse.
Motherfrog!
He's suffering more than before.
You get healing pains if you fix a big injury in a short time.
It's fine.
That just means it healed properly.
Now it's your turn, Senshi!
No, thanks.
I'll fix it myself.
But that'll take you months.
Fallon was always better at healing magic,
but I at least have the confidence of being able to heal quickly.
But...
Isn't that why it hurts so bad?
I found it!
Alright, let's begin.
It's back on!
But now it itches.
Just those healing pains at work.
Lyos, you did well.
You really managed to slay the Red Dragon.
Thanks to all of you, it was possible cause we each did our part.
I felt like we weren't gonna make it at one point.
Even I was shaking in my boots.
Guess we underestimated it, didn't we?
Eh, doesn't matter since we won.
Although...
Here, Lyos.
Kensuke!
I still haven't forgiven you regarding that thing yet.
So we'll have a long talk later.
Hmm?
Alright.
Okay.
Let's go check inside of its stomach.
Such thick skin!
We wouldn't have even reached the fat underneath if we'd fought it with Senshi's knife.
Which means, getting to the stomach could take us a while.
Want me to blow it up?
Nah.
Dragon's organs should be similar to what other creatures have.
So let's try to carve our way through bit by bit.
I hit a rib bone.
We'll have to go around it and keep on digging.
It's dark.
Should we light a lantern?
No fire.
Marcel.
Lights, please?
It's hot.
Reminds me of back when I used to work in the mines.
This is...
The stomach!
Right.
Here goes.
Empty.
But...
How?
Maybe it's a different dragon?
Not possible.
It has the same scar above its eye as the one we saw that day.
Male dragons are territorial, so I doubt there'd be many within the same vicinity.
Let's check the intestines, too.
No...
Not even a single bone has left it there.
I need to hurry and check his tongue.
Maybe it digested faster because it was moving around.
Hang on.
Here.
Huh?
Maybe it digested faster because it was moving around.
Hang on.
What is this?
A giant clump of hair and bones.
Animals that swallow their prey whole spit out the indigestible parts all at once.
However, red dragons use it as fuel for their fire breath instead.
Judging by this black fur, looks like it ate a few wargs and...
A strand of hair! Could it be?
Let's sort through it. We might find some human bones.
Hey, isn't this rod...
Laios! Look! This staff!
Valon?